Guide to the Racism Lives Here Too Movement records SC1404
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Racism Lives Here Too Movement records
2018
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SC1404
28.1 megabyte(s) 26 computer files
Scope and Contents
Includes photographs depicting Stanford Law School students with a banner stating "Racism Lives Here Too," as well as posters bearing quotes attributed to Stanford students and professors. The banner and posters were hung at Stanford Law School in February 2018 by students associated with the Racism Lives Here Too Movement.
Student movements -- California -- Stanford.; African Americans -- Civil rights -- United States.; College students, Black.; Law schools -- California.; Student demonstrations.; Students -- racism; Stanford University. School of Law
- Posters, 2018 Feb
  - Your English is so good - said at SLS, Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - You guys should take cultural appropriation as a compliment - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Disparate impact should be unconstitutional. Certain racial groups are just more obedient than others - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Minimum wage workers can’t debase themselves any further - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Minority students are not as intelligent as white students - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - How much force are the police legally allowed to use against black people? - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Can I see your Stanford ID?…There’s been so much package theft recently - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Rich people’s time is more valuable than poor people’s time - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - If someone is really starving, slavery starts to seem like a great deal. You get free food and shelter and only have to give up a few rights - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Okay, but it’s not like students at SLS experience racism. Like once you get to this level, racism doesn’t exist - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - I have trouble with Chinese names. I am much better with German or Italian names - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - I love the vibrancy and diversity of your people - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - What happened to George Zimmerman was a travesty of justice. He should never have been charged in the first place - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - I wish they would focus on diversity that actually mattered -said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Black people just commit more crime - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - An SLS student of color was personally targeted with anonymous racist hate mail. That is not the work of strangers - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Mexicans are diluting our country - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Why should we pay for the education of an illegal’s children? - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - I just don’t think Asian boys are attractive - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - How does it feel to be rich and black? You know, since most black people are poor - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - Don’t you have something to add on this discussion on racial disparities? - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - That’s such a good LSAT score for someone of your race - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
  - I forget you’re black sometimes! - said at SLS. Racism Lives Here Too, 2018-02
- Photographs, 2018 Feb
  - Racism Lives Here Too supporters, 2018-02
  - Racism Lives Here Too supporters with banner, 2018-02
  - Racism Lives Here Too supporters with banner, 2018-02